<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<statements>
	<statement id="1">It is important to investigate the impact of code reviews on <strong>defect detection or repair</strong>.</statement>
	<statement id="2">It is important to investigate the impact of code reviews on <strong>code quality</strong>.</statement>
  	<statement id="3">It is important to investigate the impact of code reviews on <strong>detection or fixes of security issues</strong>.</statement>
	<statement id="4">It is important to investigate the impact of code reviews on <strong>software design</strong>.</statement>

<statement id="5">It is important to investigate the impact of code reviews on <strong>teams' understanding of the code under review </strong>. </statement>
<statement id="6">It is important to investigate the impact of code reviews on <strong>peer impression in terms of trust, reliability, perception of expertise, and friendship</strong>.</statement>
<statement id="7">It is important to investigate the impact of code reviews on <strong>knowledge dissemination</strong>.</statement>
<statement id="8">It is important to investigate the impact of code reviews on <strong>time and motivation to contribute</strong>.</statement>
<statement id="9">It is important to investigate the impact of code reviews on <strong>developers' attitude</strong>.</statement>

<statement id="10">It is important to investigate the impact of <strong>static code analysis</strong> on the code review process.</statement> 
<statement id="11">It is important to investigate  the impact of <strong>symbolic execution</strong> on the code review process.</statement> 
<statement id="12">It is important to investigate the impact of <strong>gamification elements</strong> on the code review process.</statement>
<statement id="13">It is important to investigate the impact of <strong>continuous integration</strong> on the code review process.</statement>

<statement id="14">It is important to investigate the impact of <strong>code change descriptions</strong> on the code review process.</statement> 
<statement id="15">It is important to investigate the impact of <strong>code size changes</strong> on the code review process.</statement> 
<statement id="16">It is important to investigate the impact of <strong>commit history coherence</strong> on the code review process.</statement> 
<statement id="17">It is important to investigate the impact of <strong>review participation history</strong> on the code review process.</statement> 

<statement id="18">It is important to investigate when code reviews should be performed.</statement>  
<statement id="19">It is important to investigate what the code review benefits are, besides finding defects.</statement> 
<statement id="20">It is important to investigate how review requests are distributed (unicast, e.g. Jira, vs. broadcast, e.g. a mailing list).</statement> 
<statement id="21">It is important to investigate the efficiency and effectiveness of code reviews compared to team walkthroughs.</statement> 
<statement id="22">It is important to investigate the impact of mentioning peers in code review comments.</statement> 
<statement id="23">It is important to investigate reviews of test code.</statement> 
<statement id="24">It is important to investigate the decision making process in the code review process.</statement> 
<statement id="25">It is important to investigate the difference between pre and post-commit code reviews.</statement> 
<statement id="26">It is important to investigate strategies for merging pull requests.</statement> 
<statement id="27">It is important to investigate motivations, challenges and best practices of the code review process.</statement> 

<statement id="28">It is important to investigate the relation between review performance and reviewers’ <strong>age and experience</strong>.</statement> 
<statement id="29">It is important to investigate the relation between review performance and reviewers’ <strong>attention span</strong>.</statement> 
<statement id="30">It is important to investigate the relation between review performance and reviewers’ <strong>workload</strong>.</statement> 
<statement id="31">It is important to investigate the relation between review performance and reviewers’ <strong>social interactions</strong>.</statement> 
<statement id="32">It is important to investigate the relation between review performance and reviewers’ <strong>understanding of each other's comments</strong>.</statement> 
<statement id="33">It is important to investigate the relation between review performance and reviewers’ <strong>reviewing patterns and focus</strong>.</statement> 
<statement id="34">It is important to investigate the relation between review performance and reviewers’ <strong>perception of code quality</strong>.</statement> 

<statement id="35">It is important to investigate the difference between core and irregular reviewers in terms of <strong>the review requests amount, frequency and speed</strong>.</statement> 
<statement id="36">It is important to investigate the difference between core and irregular reviewers in terms of <strong>the activity, involvement and commitment</strong>.</statement> 
<statement id="37">It is important to investigate the difference between core and irregular reviewers in terms of <strong>the likelihood of change request acceptance</strong>.</statement> 
<statement id="38">It is important to investigate the difference between core and irregular reviewers in terms of <strong>the level of agreement between reviewers</strong>.</statement> 
<statement id="39">It is important to investigate the difference between core and irregular reviewers in terms of <strong>career paths</strong>.</statement> 
<statement id="40">It is important to investigate the difference between core and irregular reviewers in terms of <strong>the ability to find vulnerabilities</strong>.</statement> 

<statement id="41">It is important to investigate the effect of <strong>number of involved reviewers</strong> on code reviews.</statement> 
<statement id="42">It is important to investigate the effect of <strong>individual and team motivation</strong> on code reviews.</statement> 
<statement id="43">It is important to investigate the effect of <strong>fairness of code review prioritization</strong> on code reviews.</statement> 
<statement id="44">It is important to investigate the effect of <strong>satisfaction of information needs</strong> on code reviews.</statement> 

<statement id="45">It is important to investigate support for <strong>analyzing the sentiment/attitude in code reviews</strong>.</statement>
<statement id="46">It is important to investigate support for <strong>determining the usefulness of code reviews</strong>.</statement>
<statement id="47">It is important to investigate support for <strong>identifying the intention in code reviews</strong>.</statement>
<statement id="48">It is important to investigate support for <strong>estimating code review effort</strong>.</statement> 
<statement id="49">It is important to investigate support for <strong>monitoring review performance and quality</strong>.</statement> 
<statement id="50">It is important to investigate support for <strong>selection or ordering of code to review</strong>.</statement> 
<statement id="51">It is important to investigate support for <strong>selection of appropriate code reviewers</strong>.</statement> 
<statement id="52">It is important to investigate support for <strong>understanding the code changes that need to be reviewed</strong>.</statement> 
<statement id="53">It is important to investigate support for <strong>code reviews on touch-enabled devices</strong>.</statement> 
<statement id="54">It is important to investigate support for <strong>managing code reviews</strong>.</statement> 
<statement id="55">It is important to investigate support for <strong>automating code quality assessment</strong>.</statement>
<statement id="56">It is important to investigate support for <strong>estimating the review outcome</strong>.</statement>

</statements>
