<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<statements>
	<statement id="1">It is important to understad the impact of code reviews on code quality in terms of detection and/or fixes of -
		bugs, 
		post release defects, 
		software security (vulnerabilities) 
		software design (anti-patterns/code smells, TDD effectiveness), and
		program logic (fixes of conditional statements).
	</statement>
	<statement id="2">It is important to understand the code review impact on teams' understanding of the code under review, peer impression in terms of trust, reliability, perception of expertise, and friendship, knowledge dissemination, time and motivation to contribute, and developers' sentiment.</statement>
	<statement id="3">Deviating from accepted systematic review methods may introduce bias and impact the validity of the resulting rapid review, which may be an unacceptable risk for some knowledge users (practitioners).</statement>
	<statement id="4">Further research comparing the methods and results of rapid reviews and systematic reviews is required before I decide how I feel about rapid reviews.</statement>
	<statement id="5">Rapid reviews are too focused in scope and/or context to be generalizable to a variety of knowledge users (practitioners).</statement>
	<statement id="6">Rapid reviews mean different things to different people.</statement>
	<statement id="7">Rapid reviews should only precede a more comprehensive and rigorous systematic review.</statement>
	<statement id="8">The opportunity cost of a comprehensive systematic review is too high and it is more advantageous to conduct rapid reviews when timeliness is a factor.</statement>
	<statement id="9">Rapid reviews do not replace systematic reviews.</statement>
	<statement id="10">All evidence synthesis products, including rapid reviews and systematic reviews, can be conducted very well or very poorly.</statement>
	<statement id="11">Rapid reviews are comparable to systematic reviews except they are done in a more timely fashion.</statement>
	<statement id="12">Rapid reviews are quick and dirty systematic reviews.</statement>
	<statement id="13">Rapid reviews need to be tailored to the specific needs of the knowledge user (practitioners).</statement>
	<statement id="14">Rapid reviews meet the needs of knowledge users (practitioners).</statement>
	<statement id="15">There are few evidence on rapid reviews, so I cannot support or oppose their use in decision-making.</statement>
	<statement id="16">There is so much overlap across the various evidence synthesis methods that I cannot generalize my opinion to favor one over the other without the context of the decision at hand.</statement>
	<statement id="17">There is a risk involved in tailoring accepted systematic review methods to produce rapid reviews that we do not yet understand.</statement>
</statements>
